{"questions":[{"question":"QUIZ 1","answer":""},{"question":"PDF integration command cannot be used for ___________.","answer":"converting PDF files to word document"},{"question":"The following operations can be done utilizing string operation command?","answer":"All the options"},{"question":"Using Email automation command, you can directly receive emails from the server without having an Email client interface such as Gmail.","answer":"True"},{"question":"You must access to the control room to upload a bot to the control room.","answer":"True"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere cannot work with ___________.","answer":"Handwritten documents"},{"question":"In the task editor window of Automation Anywhere, you can write the code manually without using a single AA command.","answer":"False"},{"question":"On which type of clients from control room can you schedule tasks?","answer":"Runtime client"},{"question":"It is optional to offer CSV path for pattern-based data extraction in web recording.","answer":"True"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere is compatible with SAP, Oracle, Mainframes, and Java applications.","answer":"True"},{"question":"___________ is not a valid trigger type in Automation Anywhere.","answer":"system logoff"},{"question":"______ cannot be checked utilizing if condition.","answer":"cpu utilization"},{"question":"Using Email automation command, you can receive emails from the server directly without having Email client interface such as Outlook.","answer":"True"},{"question":"Web recorder can also be used to work with windows or desktop applications.","answer":"False"},{"question":"Web recorder enables us to extract tables, images, single data, and pattern-based data. The same thing can be accomplished using Smart Recorder.","answer":"False"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere offers some special variables that can be utilized inside the loop command ___________.","answer":"Excel and table column"},{"question":"Which of the following commands is more prescribed while creating a bot?","answer":"insert keystrokes"},{"question":"By utilizing Smart recorder, you can work with both web and applications.","answer":"True"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere Development client, Control Room, and Run-time Client can be installed using only one license.","answer":"False"},{"question":"Error handling command allows us to __________.","answer":"All the options"},{"question":"Meta bots are utilized in AA as a reusable component and let us work with visual captures and DLLs.","answer":"True"},{"question":"Following operations can be done utilizing string operation command?","answer":"All the options"},{"question":"Mapping of variables from main task to sub-task can be done using ___________.","answer":"Run task command"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere provides inbuilt exception handling capability","answer":"True"},{"question":"In Automation anywhere task editor window, we can manually write the lines of code without using a single AA command.","answer":"Falsef"},{"question":"Automation Anywhere offers us the flexibility to run the task by utilizing Runtime Client, Development Client, and Control Room.","answer":"False"},{"question":"You must have access to the control room to upload a bot to the control room.","answer":"True"},{"question":"On which type of clients can you schedule tasks from the control room?","answer":"Runtime client"},{"question":"Which recorder is least suggested in Automation Anywhere?","answer":"smart recorder"},{"question":"AA auto login feature permits us __________.","answer":"To execute the bot while the system is logged off"},{"question":"SQL query option under Database command can be utilized to insert, delete, and update the SQL table.","answer":"False"},{"question":"What is the exact order in Automation Anywhere - Most friendly-Moderate friendly - Least friendly formats?","answer":"Csv-scanned pdf-word"},{"question":"You can find one image in another image and do left-click, right-click and double-click using _________.","answer":"image recognition command"},{"question":"Which system variable is utilized to read the CSV and text files?","answer":"filedata column"},{"question":"Variable type that is not supported by AA is known as __________.","answer":"string"},{"question":"___________ is the command you can utilize to hold the bot execution for a particular period and then continue.","answer":"pause X hold X"}]}